Use the arrow keys to maneuver your character.
The red character Ö, which is the player, will have the following movement:
	-Up: 	Up
	-Down: 	Down
	-Left: 	Left
	-Right: Right
The green character Ö, which is the shadow, will have the following movement:
	-Up: 	Up
	-Down: 	Down
	-Left: 	Right
	-Right: Left

Both characters cannot pass through walls (represented by █) and doors.

Unlock doors (represented by ▒) using keys (represented by Θ) to advance.

If the red character Ö comes into contact with the character Ä, it will be
teleported to a random location.

If the green character Ö comes into contact with the character Ü, it will
swap places with the red character Ö.

The player will have only 800 seconds to complete the game, which has 15 levels.

There will be a time-out every 5 levels.

GLHF